Guide to the Oswald G. Villard Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Security, Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Security -Miscellaneous correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Security -DCASR, 1966-1970 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Security -Villard Consultancy, 1966-1983 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Security Violations, 1965-1972 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Shearman, E. D. R., 1972-1977 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Showen papers, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Sigma XI, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- IR&D, 1975-1979 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Ivory Coral, 1971-1975 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Ivory Coral press, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- J general, 1968-1981 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Jaye, Walter, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Journal of Geophysical Research, 1966-1972 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- DSB C3 Task Force, 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- DSB Summer Study meeting, 6/7/1968 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- DSB panel meeting, 8/7-8/1968 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- DSB meeting, 12/2-6/1968 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- DSB Summer Study, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- DSB Summer Study, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- DSB Task Force, Sidelooking Radar, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- DSB meeting, 4/12-13/1973 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- DSB meeting, 10/11-12/1973 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- DSB various publications, 1969-1973 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Superconducting Technology, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Superior Electric Company Board of Directors, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Superior Electric Company, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Babcock, James H. (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Elass, Terry & George Flammer (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Felperin, Carl (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Heideman, Michael T., 1979 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Ho, Anthony, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Lee, Daniel, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Meyer, John H., 1970 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Pitts, William M., 1965 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Sande, Craig, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Smith, Paul D., 1967 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Steffes, Paul, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Wong, Patrick, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Sturrock, Peter A., 1972-1976 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Vidman, Stuart (Box 85, Folder 11)
- NAS Sanguine, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- NAS AL Day Fund Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- NAS National Research Council meeting, 10/2-3/1968 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- NAS Satellite Panel, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- 1255 Project description and instructions, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- 1255 Project Final report draft, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- 1255 Project 1st QPR, 1/1986 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- 1255 Project 2nd QPR, 4/1986 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- 1255 Project 3rd QPR, 7/1986 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- 1255 Project transparencies, 3/1985 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- 1255 Project transparencies (Box 86, Folder 5)
- 1255 Project transparencies, 10/1986 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- 1255 Project transparencies and notes (Box 86, Folder 7)
- 1255 Project transparencies, 10/1986 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- 1255 Project technical file, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- 1255 Project technical file, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- 1255 Project original photographs (Box 86, Folder 11)
- 1255 Project weekly progress reports VOA, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- 1255 Project VOA transparencies (Box 86, Folder 13)
- 1255 Project photographs, final report (Box 86, Folder 14)
- VOA Proposal, 1977-1983 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- VOA - NAS Consultancy, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- VOA photographs, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- VOA ETU 84-121, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- VOA project file, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- VOA/RFE/RL proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- VOA HF Antennas for Skywave Reception, 1982-1983 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- VOA talk, 4/1984 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- VOA trip, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- VOA correspondence, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Improved F/B Ratios, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Processing Research Inc. (consultants), 1981 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Phillips DARPA committee, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Prince personal correspondence, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- National Research Council, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- SRI Villard performance self-evaluation, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- AFSB (Air Force Studies Board) meeting, 8/5-6/1975 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- AFSB meeting, 4/29-30/1975 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- AFSB meeting, 12/19/1974 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- AFSCAC (Air Force Systems Command Advisory Committee) meeting, 7/17-18/1974 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- AFSCAC meeting, 3/5-6/1974 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- AFSCAC meeting, 12/4/1973 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- AFSCAC, 11/7-8/1973 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- AFSCAC, 4/26-27/1973 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- AFSCAC, 1973-1975 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Proposed article QST: FRS/ORS, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- HFDF conference, 5/1982 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Stanford University subcontract under SRU ONR, antennas, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Foote, M. R., 1982 (Box 88, Folder 15)
- 2495 Project REST, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- 2495 Project REST Active, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 17)
- 2495 Project REST Passive, 1981-1983 (Box 88, Folder 18)
- 2495 Project REST Acoustic Meeting, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- 2495 Project REST Acoustics, 1980-1981 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- 5559 Project files, 1982-85 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- 5559 Project files, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- 7347 Project files, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- 7347 Project figures, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- CSI, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Proposal ETU-82-265 Informal Passive Devices, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Boulder Heating Experiment (Box 89, Folder 9)
- C general, 1965-1978 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Carribbean Hurricane & Emergency Net, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- CCIR Transeq, 1963-1966 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- C3I Coordinating Committee, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Channel, The CSU Electrical Engineering Student Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Chevron IR&D, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Chirper, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 16)
- CIA, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Coast Guard Research, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 18)
- CoCo Covert Communication, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 19)
- Craig, Joel, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 20)
- California Univ. Council on Space Sciences, 1962-65 (Box 89, Folder 21)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 22)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Leonard Committee, 1976-77 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Villard License Renewal, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Villard – Pescadero Property, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- 4268-70 [Stanford University student protests], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- LDE (Long Delayed Radio Echoes), 1971-1972 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- LDE Cassam, Dick, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- LDE QST Summary (Box 90, Folder 8)
- LDE Geomagnetic Data blanks (Box 90, Folder 9)
- LDE Hoax Probability blanks (Box 90, Folder 10)
- LDE Data sheets, Masters (Box 91, Folder 1)
- LDE Rapid Sun Magnetogram for Tillery, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- LDE Processing of Electronic Content Data - Da Rosa, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- LDE Geomagnetic Data & Delay, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- LDE Propagation Summary Reports Check, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- LDE Sonogram Scales (Box 91, Folder 6)
- LDE VI Data (Box 91, Folder 7)
- LDE Original Hoax Forms (Box 91, Folder 8)
- LDE Villard Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- LDE fo Data SRI (Box 91, Folder 10)
- LDE Graf, Cal correspondence, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- LDE Follow Up Letters Needed, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- LDE Data to Refile after Microfilming (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Antenna Patent (Robert L. Tanner), 1966 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous articles, technical reports, and catalogs, 1965-1987 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous articles, technical reports, and catalogs, 1965-1987 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- NAS meeting, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Space Science Working Group, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- IR&D (Independent Research & Development), 1974 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- NAE, 1986-1987 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- NAE - publications (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Responses to Inquiry, SRI Antennas for Reducing Interference in Shortwave Reception [VOA], Ahearn - Kaplowitz, 1990-1991 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Antennas Responses, Keeling - Weinkauf, 1990-1991 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Antennas General packet (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Antennas Documents, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Antennas Special Packet (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Antennas General Inquiries (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Antennas Follow Ups (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Antennas Survey Responses (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Antennas Evaluations (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Shortwave Radio Reception and Antennas articles, reports, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Radioscience, Microwaves articles, reports, papers, memos, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- IEEE meeting papers, 6/1979 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Photographs of the Field Site, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous notes (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- W6YX member roster, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- W6YX instruction manuals, log, 1932-1933 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Carnegie Institution Yearbook, 1984-1985 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- AAAS (American Academy of Arts & Sciences) Records, 1983-1984 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Technical Reports (Dept. of Defense) – mostly radar, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous publications, journals, newsletters, 1982-1987 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Stanford University files, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- AAAS, 1986-1987 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- NAE, 1987-1988 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous correspondence (mostly from organizations), 1986-1987 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- NAS, 1986-1987 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous technical reports, 1970-1988 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous technical reports, 1970-1988 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Bernardi, Arman (S.U.) dissertation, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- CSI experiments: Research Files by Date, 1979-1981 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- 2495 project ANA Roof Tests, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- 2495 project mono RCS Vertical Stability, 7/20/1982 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- 2495 project First Reverse Scaling, 7/1982 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Mandelkern, Dave, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Meng, Shien-Yi, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- CSIs photographs and transparencies (Box 97, Folder 9)
- photographs, transparencies, notes, presentation materials, 1980-1983 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- photographs (Box 97, Folder 11)
- CSI, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- CSI, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- CSI, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 14)
- CSI Binder, 1979-1980 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- CSI Index, 1979-1980 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Competitive Technology Advisory Committee, California State Senate, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Haggenmiller, Jack, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- California Microwave BOD correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Cannon, Robert, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Carlson, Richard W. (VOA), 1989-1990 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Cashen, John F., 1986 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Cassam, Richard, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Cattaneo, Filippo, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Cavcey, Ken, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- CCIR IWP, 10/1/1990 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Chang, John (VOA), 1991 (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Chen, Kok, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Chinese Jamming, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 15)
- Chinese Student Organizations, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 16)
- Chodorow, Marvin (SU/EE), 1989 (Box 98, Folder 17)
- Christinsin, Alan S., 1988 (Box 98, Folder 18)
- Cianos, Nick, 1974-1975 (Box 98, Folder 19)
- Clifford, John, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 20)
- Committee for Space Technology meeting, 12/4/1991 (Box 98, Folder 21)
- Committee for Space Technology report draft, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 22)
- Comstock Award, 1963-1966 (Box 98, Folder 23)
- CTI white paper, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 24)
- CTI proposal (Box 98, Folder 25)
- CTI notes, diagrams, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 26)
- CTI photographs (Box 98, Folder 27)
- CTI correspondence, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 28)
- Corum, Kenneth article, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 29)
- Cosmos Club, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 30)
- Cox, Loren, 1988-1991 (Box 98, Folder 31)
- Craighero, Roberto, 1989-1991 (Box 98, Folder 32)
- Crane, Robert, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 33)
- Crane, Hewitt, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 34)
- Crawford, F. W., 1966-1986 (Box 98, Folder 35)
- Crawford, Kent (FCC-SF), 1990 (Box 98, Folder 36)
- Croft, Tom OTHR promotion, 1989-1991 (Box 98, Folder 37)
- CSI Technological Advancement & Planning Group, 1988-1989 (Box 98, Folder 38)
- Cutler, C. Chapin, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 39)
- Danziger, Wolf, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 40)
- Da Rosa, Aldo V., 1969-1978 (Box 98, Folder 41)
- Data Communications International, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 42)
- Datong Electronics, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 43)
- Davis, John R., 1973-1981 (Box 98, Folder 44)
- Del Castillo, Ruben (VOA), 1990 (Box 98, Folder 45)
- DSB, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 46)
- Demaw, Doug, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 47)
- Recronics charts, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 48)
- Denno, S. N., 1966-1970 (Box 98, Folder 49)
- Detection of Earthquakes memos, 1989-1990 (Box 98, Folder 50)
- Development of Antennas for Anti-Jamming, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 51)
- Diaz, Jose M., 1988 (Box 98, Folder 52)
- Deminger, Walter, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 53)
- Drell, Sid, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 54)
- Dueno, Braulio, 1988-1991 (Box 98, Folder 55)
- Dueno, Braulio, 1964-1980 (Box 98, Folder 56)
- Dunlavy, John, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 57)
- DX-1 Active Antenna, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 58)
- Eash, Jospeh J., 1989 (Box 98, Folder 59)
- Edgar, Robert S., 1987 (Box 98, Folder 60)
- Edson, Bill, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 61)
- Electromagnetics Academy Who's Who, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Electrically Small Comp. Pair ESCP IEEE, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Electronics & Wireless World magazine, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Elliot, Dave, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Elliot, Kim A. (VOA), 1991 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- ERGO newsletter, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- ERG Management Council, 1988-1990 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- ERG RISC programs, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous technical reports, many from Stanford University, 1964-1985 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Adrox, Sonos, Teal Parrot (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Evans, John (NAS), 1978 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Everett, Robert, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- EW/LO Brainstorming, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- EW/Observables Steering Committee, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Fallis, Hugh, 1986-1991 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Farmer, Frank T., 1990 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- FCC Complaints, 1963-1970 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- SRI Fellowship Nomination Form, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 9)
- Fenwick, Robert B., 1988 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- Filley, Oliver, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- Fossum, Robert R., 1988 (Box 100, Folder 12)
- Foster, John S., 1989 (Box 100, Folder 13)
- Frankel, Michael S., 1988 (Box 100, Folder 14)
- Fraser-Smith, Tony, 1984-1991 (Box 100, Folder 15)
- FOIA, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Fresse, Robert E., 1985 (Box 100, Folder 17)
- Galey, William T. (Box 100, Folder 18)
- Gerson, Natahn C., 1989-1990 (Box 100, Folder 19)
- Getting, Ivan A., 1989 (Box 100, Folder 20)
- Giannini, Roger, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 21)
- Gibbons, James (SU Engineering), 1988-1989 (Box 100, Folder 22)
- Gillmor, Stewart, 1985-1989 (Box 100, Folder 23)
- Glenn, Phillip, Aquatech Controls Co., 1988 (Box 100, Folder 24)
- Goodacre, Alan, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 25)
- Goodman, Joseph, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 26)
- Graf, Calvin, 1987-1988 (Box 100, Folder 27)
- Grimes, Dale M., 1988-1989 (Box 100, Folder 28)
- Grove, Robert, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 29)
- Hagn, George, 1985-1989 (Box 100, Folder 30)
- Hagn, George 1255 project, 1985-1987 (Box 100, Folder 31)
- Hale, L. C., 1991 (Box 100, Folder 32)
- Hall, Gerald L. (QST), 1991 (Box 100, Folder 33)
- Hammett, Robert, 1988-1989 (Box 100, Folder 34)
- Haney, Tedd, 1987-1991 (Box 100, Folder 35)
- Hansen, Robert, 1988-1991 (Box 100, Folder 36)
- Harnish, Larry, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 37)
- Hately, Maurice C., 1989-1990 (Box 100, Folder 38)
- Haubenberger, Gunther, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 39)
- HAVE Forum, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 40)
- Hawker, Pat (RadComm), 1988 (Box 100, Folder 41)
- Hayden, Edgar, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 42)
- Helliwell, R. A., 1974-1990 (Box 100, Folder 43)
- Helms, Harry L., 1988-1991 (Box 100, Folder 44)
- Herrman, Dorothy, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 45)
- Hewlett, William R., 1989-1990 (Box 100, Folder 46)
- High Frequency Antennas for Skywave Reception, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 47)
- High Frequency Signal Measurements, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 48)
- Hilmy, S. M. (VOA), 1990 (Box 100, Folder 49)
- Hines, Colin, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 50)
- Holler, Dennis K., 1986 (Box 100, Folder 51)
- Holter, Marvin, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 52)
- Hoover, Herbert III, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 53)
- Horvitz, Robert, 1989-1991 (Box 100, Folder 54)
- Howard, Paul, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 55)
- IEE 4th International Conference on High Frequency Radio, 4/1988 (Box 100, Folder 56)
- IEE RFE (Radio Free Europe) Proposal, 4/1988 (Box 100, Folder 57)
- IEE/APS/URSI Symposium, 6/1989 (Box 100, Folder 58)
- IEE/APS/URSI Symposium presentation materials, 6/1989 (Box 100, Folder 59)
- IEE/APS/URSI Symposium presentation materials, 6/1989 (Box 100, Folder 60)
- LeVine, Donald J., 1988 (Box 100, Folder 61)
- IEE paper draft, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- IEE Local Jamming figures, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- IEE/SRI preprints, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Villard typescript articles, 1976-1995 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Diaz, Jose M. correspondence, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Jamming articles, reports, memos, 1985-1987 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous articles, reports, memos, 1985-1989 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Villard research notes and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Skywaves -Argus notes and data (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Kevin's measurements- loops, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous articles and notes, 1981-1985 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous articles and notes, 1983-1986 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Villard chronological files, 5-8/1990 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Villard chronological file, 9-10/1990 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Villard chronological file, 11-12/1990 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Notes & memos, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- IEEE Hagn article (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Distribution List for VOA Final Report, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- Villard articles, 1990-1991 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Respondents to QST article, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- QST article & reprint, 9/1988 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- IEEE article, master, 6/1988 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- IEEE HF Radiosystems meeting, 4/1988 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- Radio Communication (RadCom) article mention, 7/1988 (Box 101, Folder 25)
- Distribution list for IEEE, QST articles, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous notes, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 27)
- Experiments, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous notes, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 29)
- Memos, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 30)
- Notes, 1986-1994 (Box 101, Folder 31)
- Villard publications and drafts, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 32)
- notes & articles, 1988-1994 (Box 101, Folder 33)
- Vila, Ramon, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 34)
- Villard National Medal of Science Nomination Papers (Box 101, Folder 35)
- Villard gifts to Stanford University, 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 36)
- Villard ideas/draft materal, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 37)
- Vincent, Wilbur, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 38)
- Vincenti, Walter (Box 101, Folder 39)
- VLSI Implementation of Neural Networks (Box 101, Folder 40)
- Voice of June 4, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 41)
- VOA Interview draft and material, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 42)
- VOA meeting, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 43)
- WSJ article draft, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 44)
- Watkins, Dean A., 1988 (Box 101, Folder 45)
- Wattenberg, Ben (Board for International Broadcasting), 1988 (Box 101, Folder 46)
- West, Gordon, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 47)
- What Can Be Done? Article, 6/1989 (Box 101, Folder 48)
- Whelan, William T., 1988 (Box 101, Folder 49)
- White, David, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 50)
- Whyte, Ian, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 51)
- Williams, Perry, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 52)
- Yeh, K. C., 1989-1990 (Box 101, Folder 53)
- Zawawi, Mohmoud (VOA), 1990 (Box 101, Folder 54)
- URSI article, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- URSI Radio Science article & photographs, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- URSI speech, 10/20/1975 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- IEEE article offprint and photographs, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- IEEE publication, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Radio Science article "Time Delay Resolution", 1971-1972 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- QST article "LDEs, Hoaxes & the Cosmic Repeater Hypothesis" (Box 102, Folder 7)
- IEEE article "Mode Averages", 1971 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- IEEE article "Diversity Combiner" (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Radio Science article "Assessing MADC", 1972 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Radio Science article "Computer Simulation of MADC", 1973 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous reprints, photocopies, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous publications, 1973-1983 (Box 102, Folder 13)
- AAAS Election of Officers, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Villard, Collected Status Reports on "Radio Echoes of Long Delay", 1958-1960 (Box 102, Folder 15)
- NAS Terman biographical material, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 16)
- NAS Biographical Memoirs, volumes 35, 47, 51, 1987-1989 (Box 102, Folder 17)
- NAS Biographical Memoirs, volumes 53-54, 56-61, 1987-1989 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Engineering Memorial Tributes, volumes 1, 3 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Kobb, Benn, 1988-1991 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Knopes, Robert (VOA), 1990 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Kneitel, Tony, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Kho, K. S, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Kellogg, William, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Kastner, Alton (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Kabbary, F. M., 1989 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Journal of Geophysical Research, 1988-1989 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Jones, R. V., 1989-1990 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Johnson, David (ERG), 1988 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Jaye, Walter, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- Jacobs, George, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Joint Services Electronics Program, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- La Fleur, Walter (VOA), 1989-1991 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- Kraus, John, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- Kroft, David F., 1990 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- Lambert, J. A., 1982 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- Lane, George (VOA), 1988 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- Last, David, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- LDE, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 22)
- Lee, Dan, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 23)
- Lee, Mitchell, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- Legge, Roger (UHN newsletter) (Box 103, Folder 25)
- Leinwoll, Stanley, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 26)
- Leslie, Stuart, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 27)
- Lewis, John W., 1991 (Box 103, Folder 28)
- Liband, Hans, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 29)
- Lindsay, John, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 30)
- Linz, Ronald, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 31)
- Lomasney, James M., 1991 (Box 103, Folder 32)
- LDE correspondence., 1983 (Box 103, Folder 33)
- Loudin, Dave (VOA), 1991 (Box 103, Folder 34)
- Longwave Club of America- The Lowdown, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 35)
- Lunsford, Woodrow (Box 103, Folder 36)
- Morawa, Hans, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 37)
- Magnetic Absorbers (Box 103, Folder 38)
- Magnetic Power Conversion, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 39)
- Marks, Jonathan (Radio Netherlands), 1989-1991 (Box 103, Folder 40)
- Martinson, Riho (Foster City), 1990 (Box 103, Folder 41)
- May, Harold, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 42)
- Maxim Technologies, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 43)
- McAllister, Mark, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 44)
- Minimum Redundancy Arrays, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 45)
- McHenry, Mark, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 46)
- McQuivey, D. R., 1990 (Box 103, Folder 47)
- Mehring, James, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 48)
- Mesirow, Shelley, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 49)
- Messinger, R. G., 1990 (Box 103, Folder 50)
- Microwave Ferrites, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 51)
- Microwaves, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 52)
- Middleton, David, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 53)
- Miller, William F. (SRI), 1989 (Box 103, Folder 54)
- Miller, E. K., 1986 (Box 103, Folder 55)
- The Mini-State… article, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 56)
- Moell, Joe, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 57)
- Monitoring Times, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 58)
- Moxon, Les A., 1983-1992 (Box 103, Folder 59)
- Moxon, Les A., 1979-1983 (Box 103, Folder 60)